are you looking for a guaranteed benefit
well let me introduce to you our Sun
Life traditional product sun smarter
life elite Let's have a quick review
about this
product sun smarter life elite lets you
enjoy this benefits number one 200% of
the face amount number two lifetime
guaranteed cash benefits number three
living benefits and number four flight
premium
payments Okay let's start so first of all
it has life insurance coverage of
200% of the face amount example if you
have php500,000 face amount  you have a 1
million life insurance coverage up to
age 100 let me repeat life insurance
coverage up to age
100 number two lifetime guaranteed cash
benefit take note of the first two words
lifetime means lifetime and
guaranteed
guaranteed let me show this
illustration to you based on zero age
male child insured
4.2% accumulation rate 500,000 face
amount take note that the endowment
benefit of our Suns smarter life elite
is 88% of our basic faam
so  500,000 Tim 8%  is equal to 40,000
endowment benefit payouts every other
year so he will start at the end of the
6th Year of the client's policy so since
our insurance is still at zero age
his endowment benefit will start
at the age of 6 and to follow at the age
of 8 every other year until age 100
so 40,000 is guaranteed to be given to
him always but you noticed there is an
accumulation or
accumulated amount on the side what that means
if he doesn't take his 40,000 from
Sunlife his 40,000
will still earn and will be 83,000
186 at the age of 12 it will be 181 785 at
the age of 14 237
376 and up to age 100 if he doesn't
move it it will be
2,776
[Music]
let's proceed to the living benefits or
non guaranteed benefits these are the
dividends which is based on company  per
per month and not guaranteed but you can
accumulate or you can receive it in cash
pangalawa is the cash value which is
You can get a loan with minimum
interest per anum and the next the
portion of the face amount will be given
to the life to be ensured if diagnosed
to be terminally
ill and because Sun Life will no longer make us suffer
in paying our
premiums it has flexible premium
payments so we have three
options annual semi-annual and the
minimum is quarterly itong monthly because
it is only available through auto debit
or autocharge since our policy sun
smarter life elite is a traditional product
but before you can apply for monthly
payment you need to
complete the quarterly payment at the
tion of the policy before you can to
monthly
payment and of course
the policy must be settled
before Besides the above benefits
we also have additional Riders or
supplementary benefits that can be
attached to our sun smarter life elite
product blood number one the total
disability benefit number two The
Accidental death benefit number three
the cib or critical illness benefit
number four hib or hospital  income
benefit Number 5 wpd or wdd waver of
premium this waver of premium is
only available when our insured
is a minor And he has an initial
owner and because we think in advance we
know you will ask how
long it can be
paid we have three ways
how long we can pay
sun smarter life elite So you can
pay him for 5 years only 10 years
or regular pay but with our regular pay
you will pay him for your whole life but
you also have the chance to pay only a
shorter period of time for your whole life if you don't
move your accumulated
dividends and accumulated endowment
benefits because this can also be used to
cover what you will pay with regular pay and
that is where our quick
product review about Suns marter life
elite you may reach out through my email
flash on the screen or any Sun Life
Financial advisor for more information
Thank you and have a bright day